Shyen Wee.

441	401	152	152

shyen.wee@gmail.com

github.com/fractalfeeling

Summary

Analytical problem solver specialising in creative solutions, passionate about meaningful data and highly motivated by opportunities to fill gaps in existing processes with bespoke and novel solutions.

Driven self-starter learns through facing challenges head on, demonstrated previously in fast-paced high demand parliamentary role. Responsibilities included monitoring news flows and social media interactions, crafting time critical responses over a wide range of media.

Technical	Programming	Web Development	Management Systems
	C, Python, SQL, Linux	HTML5, CSS, Javascript	Nationbuilder CRM/CMS, Moodle LMS
	Design	e-Commerce	Marketing

Career

Electorate Officer - Parliament of Australia

Feb 2018-Jun 2019 / Kent Town, SA

- → Administration and management of Nationbuilder including data export and data cleansing
- → Analyse data from Facebook, Twitter and Nationbuilder providing insights to PR Director and Media Advisor for continuous improvement of social media content and delivery
- ightharpoonup Optimise Facebook Ads using Lookalike Audiences and Customer Lifetime Value—achieving Facebook page follower growth of ~28% over 3 months
- → Manage email campaigns—including weekly newsletter with donation appeal to ~80,000 people—achieving consistent open rate of 24-30% and bounce rate of <1% through email deliverability best practices, A/B testing and data validation on forms
- → Deliver election campaign material nationwide through SMS/MMS—over 1 million messages sent—with automated replies based on trigger keywords
- → Produce digital content consistent with brand and style guides and print collateral for election and fundraising campaigns compliant with AEC guidelines

IT & Technical Support Officer - Australian Institute of Technology Transfer

Apr 2011-Sep 2017 / Elizabeth, SA

- \rightarrow Research and implement IT systems to increase productivity—implementations include setting up a local file server, router with security firmware for local WiFi management and digitisation of paper based feedback form system
- → Set up and manage Moodle student learning management system
- → Create documentation and train staff on Moodle LMS
- → Prepare reports from VETtrak data, compliant with AVETMISS reporting requirements
- → Provide technical support and maintenance of company IT assets

Projects / Volunteer

Student Mentor - 42 Adelaide

May-Jun 2022 / Adelaide, SA

- → Volunteer student mentor for the May 2022 Piscine—28-day school admission bootcamp
- \rightarrow Support prospective students on-campus and remotely, building on my past experiences to provide advice and guidance

Website Development and Marketing - Hanamura

April 2020 / Modbury, SA

- → Build website with ordering and notification system to handle influx of online orders during the pandemic—hanamura.com.au
- ightarrow Generate Lookalike Audiences for ad targeting based on existing customer data
- → Optimise Facebook Ads for customer location

Education

42 Cursus (Coding School)

Jan 2022-Present / 42 Adelaide

Certificate IV in Work Health and Safety

2014 / Australian Institute of Technology Transfer